

ABOUT ME

I am a Junior Full Stack Developer with experience in web technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript, and advanced proficiency in frameworks and libraries like React and Node.js. I have knowledge in SQL databases and backend implementation TypeScript.

CONTACT

678567628

annahico@gmail.com

Barcelona Ciudad

Portfolio

LinkedIn

GitHub

STAKS

- HTML5
- REACT
- CSS3
- MYSQL
- JAVASCRIPT EXPRESS
- GIT
- GITHUB
- TYPESCRIPT

- BOOTSTRAP
- NODE.JS

LANGUAGES

- Catalan Native
- · Spanish Native
- English C2
- German A2



HIDALGO COSTA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

HIGH SCHOOL TEACHER

CONSORCI BARCELONA

2022 - Present

Teach English language skills (reading, writing and speaking) to secondary and high school students. Prepare and adapt educational materials, evaluating academic progress. Foster an inclusive and motivating learning environment.

CUSTOMER SERVICE

FTT

2015-2022

Provide support and solutions to customer queries, ensuring customer satisfaction. Manage and resolve complaints efficiently. Maintain accurate and up-to-date records of customer interactions.

EDUCATION

BOOTCAMP FULL STACK DEVELOPER

GeeksHubs

2024

UNIVERSITY MASTER'S DEGREE IN EDUCATION AND ICT

Universitat Oberta de Catalunya, UOC

UNIVERSITY MASTER'S DEGREE TEACHER TRAINING

Blanquerna, URL

POSTGRADUATE EDUCATIONAL DIRECTION AND **LEADERSHIP**

Universitat Oberta de Catalunya, UOC

DEGREE IN ENGLISH STUDIES

Universitat de Barcelona. UB 2015-2020

ERASMUS 2018-2019

PROJECTS

JavaScript Logic Project

Shopping Cart

Interactive TV Project

Back-end Project

Restaurant Menu Project